



User Interviews and Surveys

Requirements and User Stories

Wireframing and Prototyping

Layout, Typography and Style Guides

Developing Business Cases and SOPs

Project Management Skills

Workshop Facilitation

User Journey Mapping

User Personas

User Testing

Agile DSDM

UI / Visual Design

User Research and Competitor Analysis

Design Skills

Profile

I am a Service / UX Designer passionate about the key role of design in bridging the gap between technology's potential to make the world a better place and the realisation of this in the form of better health, wellbeing and social mobility. With my previous experience spanning across service / UX design, project management, consulting, data analytics, operational improvement and team leadership, I have a versatile skillset to bring a holistic approach to my work. I have a **portfolio** of 4 projects, my own website I designed and developed from scratch using CSS, HTML and JavaScript, as well as, design experience within the NHS, Cancer Research UK and a health start up called Healum.

Education

Apr 2023 - May 2023

The Knowledge Academy

Agile Project Management Foundation & Practitioner (AgilePM®) and Scrum Master Certification

June 2020 - Feb 2023

CareerFoundry

UX/UI course including cross platform design and web development, during which <u>4 projects</u> were completed.

Sept 2019 - Oct 2021

Birmingham University

Elizabeth Garrett Anderson Postgraduate Diploma in Health Leadership, **Distinction**.

Oct 2013 - June 2017

Durham University

Bachelor of Science in Business, Computer Science and Economics, First Class Honours.

Skills



M

MURAL

HTML

5

HTML

PYTHON



MIRO

JAVA





SKETCH













SQL

Data Analysis Skills

Process Flow Mapping

Project Timelines

Risk Management

Stakeholder Management

Project Progress Tracking

Intermediate SQL Advanced Microsoft Excel PowerQuery

Employment

Oct 2021 - May 2022

Oncology Service Design / Improvement Manager at Royal Orthopaedic Hospital NHS Foundation Trust

- Achieved improvements to patient experience along the cancer pathway through: supporting effective collaboration between staff along the cancer pathway, facilitating co-creation of process changes and coordinating the implementation of iterative changes together.
- Successfully led efforts to clear the significant backlog of over 1000 clinical letters discovered upon commencing my role. This was achieved through engaging all key stakeholders to map out the process and its bottlenecks, facilitating discussions around solutions, getting the buy in from all key stakeholders and coordinating implementation of improvements. Letter turnaround time reduced from over 20 days in October 2021 to 7-10 days by March 2022.
- Directly managed a total of eleven staff and recruited to multiple vacancies within the team which involved: shortlisting, interviewing and onboarding.

June 2021 - Sept 2021

User Experience Intern at Healum

- Worked within an agile environment carrying out user testing with patients and health and social care professionals on version 1 of Healum's app and communicated findings at regular intervals to the product manager, software engineers and project manager.
- Led user research activities which informed how their health and wellbeing app could be tailored better towards people with diabetes and obesity. User research activities included secondary research, planning and conducting user interviews and focus groups.
- A final report was produced including key themes and user stories for proposed new features. This research inspired the app design for WEIInUS, one of the projects within my course portfolio, for which I produced user flows, low, mid and high fidelity wireframes, a style guide and interactive iOS and Android prototypes.

Sept 2019 - June 2021

Service Design / Integration Manager at NHS Leadership Academy

- Organised and facilitated workshops and process mapping activities between key health and social care stakeholders using Miro, Mural and Figma. This enabled them to work collaboratively and improve on 60 existing services to enhance patient experience along the hospital discharge pathway.
- Played an instrumental role in the design and implementation of a new primary care service called the Healthy Ageing Coordinator service. This involved production of induction materials and SOPs for new staff, as well as, developing promotional posters, a video and patient success stories to promote the value of the service.
- Successfully coordinated user discovery activities with over 400 individuals aged 60+ to gain an in depth picture of digital literacy in our local area during COVID. This involved creating a telephone survey, coordinating its completion and producing an infographic which I presented at Board level.
- Successfully liaised with key Children and Young People (C&YP) stakeholders to develop a model and business case for a pilot of community joint clinics and multidisciplinary meetings between GPs, consultants and key C&YP professionals.

July 2019 - Aug 2019

Summer Intern in Technology at Cancer Research UK

- My first insight into a UI/UX career, during which I received an Employee Appreciation for facilitating user lab testing on an Alexa quiz prototype.
- Led a project to rejuvenate CRUK's Technology recruitment page. This involved: leading workshops around content prioritisation, interviewing employees, using storytelling techniques and copywriting.
- Successfully led an Afternoon Light Bites event which made a £400 profit. This involved securing food donations from high profile brands and innovative marketing using QR codes.
- Co-created sections of a best practice catalogue for Technology employees through facilitating workshops with Technology leads from each team in the department.

Oct 2017 - June 2019

Technology Associate at KPMG

- Received four Encore Awards for my commitment to delivering high quality work and consistently excelling at fulfilling an experienced professional role on projects. These projects typically involved: managing various stakeholder relationships, process mapping, conducting stakeholder interviews and writing reports or presentations.
- · My achievements included: conducting a thematic analysis of an IT Customer Satisfaction survey for a client and presenting this to their IT Leadership team, supporting an IT control redesign project in Amsterdam for one of the largest travel companies in the world and creating a project status dashboard for a client under a pressurised deadline.